Rothstein, Richard Collection of ACWA-ACTWU Files 6142
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Misc. Hearings BLS etc Folder 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Misc. Hearings BLS etc Folder 2 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Textile Machinery Ind. (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Hard Bargaining Ahead (Box 20, Folder 13)
- OTA Draft (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Cline Future Textile Trade (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Ridgewood Knitwear (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Puerto Rico Apparel (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Hufbauer- Trade Policy FDR Troubled Ind. (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Cuomo Draft (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Fed TR. Comm: Import Quotas on Textiles (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Hufbauer- Trade Protection (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Ghadar: US Industrial Competitiveness (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Competitive Status of US Fibers Complex (Box 20, Folder 23)
- World Bank Textile Ind. (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Chinatown Study (Box 20, Folder 25)
- California Joint Board vs. Chase Bag Company Folder 1 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- California Joint Board vs. Chase Bag Company Folder 2 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Various Contracts and Agreements (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Rules, Agreement Form, Insurance (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Xerox Corp. vs. ACTWU- Lance Charles (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Xerox Corp. vs. ACTWU- Lance Charles (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Xerox Corp. vs. ACTWU- Lance Charles (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Xerox Corp. vs. ACTWU- Lance Charles: Appeal (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Union Officer Training Materials Folder 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Union Officer Training Materials Folder 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Press Releases (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Grievance Appeal Procedure (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Southern California Joint Board (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Nuclear Freeze, El Salvador, Congressional Profiles, Euromissiles (Box 21, Folder 12)
- American Laser/HGM/Loral (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Xerox Corp- Margarita Andara (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Pace Line (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Various Union Publications (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Arbitration (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Magazine, Newspaper Articles (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Bay Area Clothing (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Target Forms (Box 21, Folder 20)
- EOS Organizing (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Notes, Data, Addresses (Box 21, Folder 22)
- CILCO Pomona (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Jan Martin Folder 1 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Jan Martin Folder 2 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Claude Cox vs. Richard Rothstein, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  9-Dec-83
- Claude Cox vs. Richard Rothstein, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  10-Dec-83
- El Salvador Scrapbook (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Rochester Job Classification, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Rochester Timelines/OA, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Diablo Jordan, Manley, Troxler, Hemming, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Involuntary O.T., Leaving Without Permission, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Rochester Industrial Engineering, Production Bonus Plan, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Hayward Discharge Shop Chair, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Rochester Discharge Unauthorized Leaving Work Area, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Rochester Part Time Couns' (Yannatone), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Rochester Subcontracting Impact, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Rochester Discharge for Threatening Superior, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Rochester Bargaining Unit Work, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Rochester Definition of Job Requirements (Q.C.), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Blauvelt Absenteeism Suspensions, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Atlanta EE Doctor vs. Company DR., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Rochester Jurisdiction ACWA vs. I.U.D.E., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Rochester Late Pay Checks, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Rochester Production Bonus, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Rochester Performance of B.U. Work, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Rochester Overtime Assignment, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Rochester Promotion, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Rochester Overtime Distribution, Seniority, Call in Pay, Transfers, Snow Emergency, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Rochester Promotion, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Rochester Shift Rotation Schedule, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Rochester Job Assignments, Release for Union Bus., New Jobs, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Rochester Discharge/Absenteeism, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Rochester Temporary Transfers, Cut Back Priority, Production Bonus, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Rochester Production Bonus, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Opening Statement- Hemming (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Opening Statement- Manley (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Opening Statement- Troxler (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Opening Statement- Timelines (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Opening Statement- Jordan (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Agreements and Contracts: Rocky Mountain District Joint Board (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Agreements and Contracts: Rocky Mountain District Joint Board, Gerico, Steiner Corporation (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Camp 7- Grievances and Arbitration Pending (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Camp 7 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Camp 7 Proposals (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Camp 7 Negotiations- Notes (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Case Preparation (Box 22, Folder 40)
- FMCS (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Arbitrators- Biographical (Box 22, Folder 42)
- A.A.A. (Box 22, Folder 43)
- CA Unemployment Compensation (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Workers Compensation (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Officer's Manual (Zwirner Draft) (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Local Union Organizing Committees (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Health and Safety Committees (Box 22, Folder 48)
- "Organizing the Organized" (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Local Union Meetings (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Threads Program (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Education Committees (Box 22, Folder 52)
- Officers Training- Sheets (Box 22, Folder 53)
- Membership Committees (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Newsletter Committees (Box 22, Folder 55)
- Oregon AFL-CIO "Local Union Tool" (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Social Service Committees (Box 22, Folder 57)
- Political Action Committee (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Political Action Committee (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Public Speaking (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Training Programs- Agendas (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Union Structure (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Officers Training (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Collective Bargaining-Role Playing (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Photos-Gerico (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Health and Welfare Plan- ACTWU (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Union Articles, Dollars and Sense, Directory of Unions and Employee Associations (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Irvine (Box 23, Folder 11)
- L.A. (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Copies of Literature (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Bill Gomez (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Contributions (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Lists of Members and Local Unions (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Jack Sheinkman File (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Levi-Strauss and El Salvador (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Internal Union Issues (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Membership, Convention Information (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Frank Nicholas (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Nuclear Freeze/Economics of Warfare (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Mid and Deep South Regional Conference (Box 23, Folder 23)
- "The Reality of Today, the Hope for Tomorrow" (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Material from Training Conferences (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Collective Bargaining Proposals (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Union Financial and Membership Information (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Electro Optical/Local 1414F Folder 1 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Electro Optical/Local 1414F Folder 2 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Electro Optical/Local 1414F Folder 3 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Nuclear Freeze Campaign (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Various Union Publications (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Brand Name Directory (Box 23, Folder 33)
- OSHA, Steven's Propaganda, Union Startup and Information (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Sbicca Negotiation (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Agreement Between Xerox Corp. and Locals 14F and 14Y (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Minutes, Bay Area Clothing, Arbitration Requests, Colshire, Diablo, Xerox (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Action Newsletter, Xerox Agreements (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Century Data Systems- Union and Company Proposals (Box 24, Folder 6)
- "Unionism in the Southern Textile Industry: An Overview" Bruce Raynor (Box 24, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens Speeches and Outlines (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Various Surveys, Statistics and Pamphlets Folder 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Various Surveys, Statistics and Pamphlets Folder 2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Directories, Guides, and "A Curriculum in Labor History" (Box 24, Folder 11)
- American Labor History (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Handbook of Labor Statistics, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Dollars and Sense, Viewpoint, Major Labor Law Principles, Green Mountain Quarterly, What to Do When the Union Knocks (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Bayly Workers, Agreement Between Century Data and ACTWU (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Local Research Guide for Organizers (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Exhibits, Copies, and Opening Notes Folder 1 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Exhibits. Copies, and Opening Notes Folder 2 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Newspaper Articles, Pamphlets, "Perspective on Organizing the New Breed Packinghouse Worker" (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Headwear Negotiations (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Mobile Health Center (Box 24, Folder 21)
- UAW Chrysler (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Nuclear Weapons Freeze Initiative (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Memos to Mejia (Box 25, Folder 3)
- McFadden Economic Issues Manual (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Labor Committee for Safe Energy and Full Employment (Box 25, Folder 5)
- OSHA- Health and Safety (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Xerox, Newsletters (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Starting Unions- Information Packet (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Discharge- Antonin Bartosik (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Sbicca Folder 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Sbicca Folder 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Cassettes (Box 25, Folder 12)
- LocalC- Local By-Laws Xerox (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Local 14Z (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Local 14Y (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Comm. on Potentially Revised Contracts (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Clothing Industry Statistics (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Local 1414G (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Zodys Folder 1 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Zodys Folder 2 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Zodys Folder 3 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Zodys Folder 4 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Local 1414F (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Memorandum Drafts (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Dues Information and Problems Folder 1 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Dues Information and Problems Folder 2 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Financial Information and Expenses (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Agreements, Charges and Negotiations (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Local 1414C Hayward California (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Rules and Regulations- English and Spanish (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Local 14T (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Withdrawn/Dropped Grievances (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Arbitration Agreements (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Stevens Wage Settlement (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Textile Works Wage Information (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Information and Requests (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Disc. Warnings (Box 26, Folder 8)
- United States of America Before the National Labor Relations Board (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Gerico (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Ahora Magazine (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Elections, Labor Disputes, Union Information- Gerry Alamosa (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Gerico (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) posters. (4 ) (Box 27)
- ACTWU posters. (6 ) (Box 28)
- ACTWU posters. (5 ) (Box 29)
- J.P. Stevens posters. (3 ) (Box 30)
- J.P. Stevens posters. (5 ) (Box 31)
- J.P. Stevens posters. (5 ) (Box 32)
- J.P. Stevens posters. (6 ) (Box 33)
- J.P. Stevens posters. (5 ) (Box 34)